

PORTUGUESE NATIVE, ENGLISH C1

Sao Paulo, Brazil +55 12 99646-0749 cauane.emanuela@hotmail.com github.com/CauaneAndrade linkedin.com/in/CauaneAndrade

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a software developer with 4 years of experience using Python, JavaScript, Rust, SQL query and GIS technologies for areas like Agricultural lending, environmental regularization, U.S. electricity and natural gas holding companies.

I have knowledge in Docker containers, and processes that improves software engineering best practices like git, CI/CD pipelines, JIRA Suite, DevOps, etc.

I also have knowledge and experience working with location data in multiple tools/platforms such as GeoDjango, OpenLayers, ArcGIS.

Experience in data analysis, metrics, monitoring systems.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Faculdade de Tecnologia de São Paulo Bachelor of Technology, System Analysis and Development

2018 – Jul 2022

FATEC is a Conceive Design Implement Operate (CDIO) collaborator. System Analysis and Development student.

Escola Técnica Estadual de São Paulo Marketing Technician, Marketing 2017 – 2018

ETEC is a government program aimed at training technical level professions.

Marketing Technician student.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHT

Junior Software Engineer II TerraMagna

Feb 2022 - Present | Sao Paulo, Brazil

TerraMagna is a Agri/Fin Tech focused on managing credit risk for Agricultural lenders, including input distributors, trading firms, banks, and co-ops.

Software engineer developing APIs and web interfaces, remote sensing technologies, service deployment, ETL activities (data transformation/cleaning, web scraping, real-time data synchronization).

Skills: Python, Rust (async), TypeScript (React.js), Bazel, PostgreSQL/PostGIS, BigQuery, Google Cloud Platform (cloud function, schedulers), Sentinel Hub, Unix/Linux.

Junior Software Engineer High Desert Spatial

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022 | New Mexico, United States

High Desert Spatial is a global company that provides software development and GIS services to the utility industry.

Engineer responsible for creating workflows to synchronize databases, automation process, API development, operational and informational dashboard development, Portal maintenance.

Skills: ArcGIS products, ArcGIS API for Python/ArcPy, Web AppBuilder, PowerShell, CA Workload Automation, Oracle (standard and geographic), Java Spring Boot, IBM Maximo, Windows.

Junior Software Developer Necto Systems

Mar 2019 - Mar 2021 | Sao Paulo, Brazil

Necto Systems is a company specialized in on-demand software development and consulting, focused on Data Science and GIS projects.

Full stack developer responsible for implementing APIs and web solutions, database integrations, data analysis for government agencies.

Skills: Django/Django Rest Framework, Vue.Js, Docker/Compose, OpenLayers, GeoDjango, PostgreSQL/postgis, Robot Framework, Bash, CI/CD, Unix/Linux.